No other option than cake?
No, not kheer,
not halwa, halwa, yuck, not cake, I feed you a different type of
cake.  Come, let
me feed you pancakes today.  Pancake, did
your pancake taste good?
Hey, I will make Pintola with high protein muesli.
In this you will get 25 grams of protein in 100 grams.  There is
no refined sugar but there are nuts and seeds, so that's good, is
n't it?   It
happened, right?
Now go ahead.
Hey, do
n't touch a chain beyond your means.
What did you say to him?
Pancakes.   I should have
told you earlier that I was going to feed you Malpua.
I don't want to eat your pan.
Hey, it will be done brother.   Please
Keep.
Hey brother, was it going to be like this?
Otherwise, wouldn't you have said the same to me?
Safe Master Safe Master Blaster.
Come come, it's done.  Batsman Batsman
DJ.